Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee College of Letters & Science Records, 1948-2014
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1948-2014, UWM Archival Collection 1; 73.9 cubic ft. (83 boxes)
  - 1. Subject Files, 1948-2014
    - Dept. of Economics
      - Graduate Program Reviews, 1976-1979 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Dept. of English
      - 1973-1984 (Box 12, Folder 15-29)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
      - Graduate Program Reviews, 1974-1979 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Dept. of French and Italian
      - 1973-1986 (Box 13, Folder 3-6)
      - Planning Document, 1983 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Dept. of Geography
      - 1974-1986 (Box 13, Folder 7-12)
      - Planning Document, 1983-1984 (Box 57, Folder 13)
      - Program Reviews, 1974-1977 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Dept. of Geological and Geophysical Sciences, 1979-1986 (Box 13, Folder 13-15)
    - Dept. of Geological Sciences
      - 1973-1978 (Box 13, Folder 16-18)
      - Earth and Atmospheric Sciences, PhD Proposal, 1972-1978 (Box 60, Folder 17)
      - Five Year Review, 1973-1979 (Box 60, Folder 18)
      - Review of Existing Academic Program, 1973? (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Dept. of German
      - 1964, 1973-1986 (Box 13, Folder 19-23)
      - Planning Documents, 1982-1984 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Dept. of Governmental Affairs, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Dept. of Hebrew Studies, 1973-1986 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Dept. of History
      - 1956-1966 (Box 13, Folder 26-28)
      - 1973-1978 (Box 13, Folder 29-30)
      - 1979-1986 (Box 14, Folder 1-5)
      - Graduate Reviews, 1973-1979 (Box 60, Folder 19)
      - PhD Proposal, undated (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Dept. of Language Laboratories
      - 1959-1968, undated (Box 60, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, 1958-1970 (Box 60, Folder 22-23)
    - Dept. of Learning Skills, 1969-1983 (Box 14, Folder 6-7)
    - Dept. of Linguistics
      - 1963-1986 (Box 14, Folder 8-11)
      - Planning Document, 1983-1984 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Dept. of Mass Communication
      - 1973-1986 (Box 14, Folder 12-21)
      - 1985 (Box 80, Folder 4)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Audit, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - Community Advisory Committee, Broadcast Subcommittee, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Community Advisory Committee, Newspaper Venture, 1979-1981 (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - Crossroads Newspaper, 1974-1976 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - Planning Document, 1981-1982 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - School of Journalism, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - UWM Central Program Newspaper Workshop for Minorities, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Dept. of Mathematical Sciences
      - 1973-1986 (Box 14, Folder 26-30)
      - Graduate Program Review, 1979 (Box 60, Folder 24)
      - Planning Documents, 1983-1985 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Dept. of Military Science, Planning Document, 1983-1984 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Dept. of Pharmacy
      - Correspondence, 1965-1973 (Box 60, Folder 25-26)
      - Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - Dept. of Philosophy, 1974-1986 (Box 15, Folder 1-3)
    - Dept. of Physics
      - 1972-1986 (Box 15, Folder 4-11)
      - Planning Document, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Program Review, 1973-1979 (Box 60, Folder 28)
      - Undergraduate Program Review, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - Dept. of Political Science
      - 1973-1986 (Box 15, Folder 12-15)
      - Graduate Program Review, 1973-1979 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Dept. of Psychology
      - 1974-1986 (Box 15, Folder 16-23)
      - Program Review, 1972-1979 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Dept. of Slavic Languages, 1973-1986 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Dept. of Sociology
      - 1973-1986 (Box 15, Folder 24-28)
      - Planning Document, 1982-1984 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Planning Document, 1984-1985 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Program Review, 1973-1978 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Dept. of Spanish and Portuguese
      - 1973-1979 (Box 15, Folder 29-31)
      - 1980-1986 (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
      - Planning Documents, 1980-1985 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Dept. of Speech Pathology and Audiology, 1971-1975 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Dept. of Urban Affairs
      - 1973-1985 (Box 16, Folder 5-7)
      - Program Review, 1973-1974 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Program Review, 1977-1979 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Dept. of Zoology
      - 1972-1984 (Box 16, Folder 8-13)
      - Five Year Graduate Program Review, 1974, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Development Committee, 1976-1983 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Directory of Awards, Grants and Fellowships: Primarily in Letters and Science, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Distinguished Professor Committee, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Division of Urban Outreach
      - 1973-1986 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Committee of Five, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Divisional Committees, 1970-1976 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Divisional Membership Lists, 1973-1975 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Double Majors in Business and Foreign Language, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Downer Seminary Property, 1957-1960 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Drug Analysis Center, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Economics, Whitefish Bay High School, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Educational Opportunity Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Elvenhjem, Conrad A., 1959-1962 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - English as a Second Language, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - English Composition, 1979-1985 (Box 16, Folder 28-31)
    - English for Foreign Students, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - English Proficiency Testing, 1976-1981 (Box 16, Folder 33-34)
    - English Writing Lab
      - 1973 (Box 16, Folder 35)
      - English Writing Lab, 1975-1979 (Box 17, Folder 1-4)
    - English-Comparative Literature Dispute, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Enough Said, 1997-1999 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Enrollment
      - 1956-1958 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - 1972-1976 (Box 17, Folder 6-7)
      - 1981-1988 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Enrollment Task Force, 1978-1980 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Environmental Studies
      - 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Environmental Studies Course Work Coordination Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Ethnic Studies Brochure, Undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Ethnic Studies Committee, 1971-1977 (Box 17, Folder 13-15)
    - Ethnic Studies Program
      - 1978-1982 (Box 17, Folder 16-17)
      - BA Proposal, 1974-1978 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Excavation of Indian Remains, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Executive Committee, 1956-1967 (Box 17, Folder 20-22)
    - Experimental Program in Higher Education, 1970-1977 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Extension Division, 1958-1966 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - External Degrees Program, 1972-1975 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Faculty Committees, Membership Lists, 1969-1976 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Faculty Development Plan, 1978-1985 (Box 17, Folder 27-28)
    - Faculty Exchange Program, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Faculty Meetings
      - 1956-1971 (Box 17, Folder 30-35)
      - 1972-1991 (Box 18, Folder 1-11)
    - Faculty Promotions, 1974-1995 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Recognition Dinner, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Faculty Retirement Guidebook, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Welfare Committee, 1971-1974 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Fairy Chasm Preserve, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Field Stations, 1963-1985 (Box 18, Folder 15-17)
    - Film Program, Planning Document, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Film Studies Program, 1972-1985 (Box 18, Folder 18-20)
    - First Dean's Day Program on Unfinished Business in American History, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - First Friday, 1977-1980 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - The First Ten Years, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Five-Year Reviews of Graduate Programs, 1974-1981 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Five-Year Study of Faculty Salaries, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Foreign Language Film Society, 1971-1973 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Language Liaison Committee, 1973-1985 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Foreign Language Merger Task Force, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Forum 1977, Audio reels (¼ in.) (Box 18, Folder 29-30, Audio 1-4)
    - Forum 1977, Videocassette (U-matic) (Box 19, Folder 1-4, Video 1-4)
    - Forum 1977 Presented at the Conference (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Foundation Funding, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Freshman Forum
      - 1956-1970 (Box 62, Folder 2-3)
      - 1959 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Programs, 1959-1969 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Freshman Guidelines, 1974-1977 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Freshman Orientation, 1978-1981 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Freshman Seminar Program, 1971-1977 (Box 19, Folder 9-14)
    - General Curriculum and Standard Curriculum Comparative Study, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - General Education Requirements Committee, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - General Education Requirements on Foreign Language Enrollments, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Germany Trip (Canceled), 1979 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Giessen Trip, Justus-Liebig-Universitat, 1981-1983 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Golda Meir Lecture Series, 1979-1983 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Governor Lucey's Letter to President Weaver, 1972 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Grading Report, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 18-19)
    - Graduate Assistants Stipends, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Graduate Program Committee, 1978-1986 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Graduate Program Development, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Graduate School
      - 1956-1968 (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - 1972-1984 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Greene Hall, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Greene Museum Committee Report and Related Materials, 1994-1995 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Grievance Procedures, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Growth and Development of the College of Letters and Science, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Guggenheim Fellowship, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Harrington, Frederick, 1958-1968 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Harris, Fred R., 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Hearing Evaluation Center, 1956-1963 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - High School Counselors, 1977-1983 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - High School Relations, 1963-1966 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - History of Science, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Holton Hall Drawing Room Committee, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Holton Hall Rededication Committee
      - 1972, 1979-1981 (Box 79, Folder 2-3)
      - Photographs and Slides, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Home Economics, 1958-1967 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Honorary Degrees Committee, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Honors Program, 1956-1986 (Box 20, Folder 13-27)
    - Human Growth and Development Curriculum Committee, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Human Resources Program, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Human Services PhD, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Humanities and Communications Area, 1974-1989 (Box 20, Folder 31-34)
    - Humanities BA, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Humanities Building, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 36-37)
    - Humanities Faculty, circa 1956 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Humanities PhD, 1973-1975 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Indirect Cost Recovery, 1978-1980 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Industrial and Labor Relations, 1976-1982 (Box 21, Folder 2-7)
    - Institute of World Affairs
      - 1959-1964 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - 1978-1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Institutional Studies Reports
      - 1956-1958 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - 1958-1961 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - 1966 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Instructional Media Laboratory, 1972-1976 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Integrated Arts and Sciences Program, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Integrated Liberal Studies, 1969-1972 (Box 21, Folder 15-18)
    - Integrated Research Program, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Inter-American Institute of Ecology, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Inter-Semester Period, 1971-1975 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - International Major Advisory Committee, 1967-1977 (Box 21, Folder 22-23)
    - International Relations Major
      - 1957-1967 (Box 21, Folder 24-25)
      - 1972-1983 (Box 21, Folder 26-27)
      - Planning Documents, 1982-1983 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - J. Max Patrick Collection, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Kraynick, Ted, 1965-1967 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Language and Literature Committee
      - 1969-1974 (Box 21, Folder 31-34)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 35)
      - Advisory Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Advisory Committee, 1976-1990 (Box 22, Folder 2-4)
    - Language and Literature PhD Proposal Committee, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Language Chairmen's Group, 1966-1982 (Box 22, Folder 6-12)
    - Language Laboratories
      - Advisory Committee, 1973-1985 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Planning Document, 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Planning Document, 1984-1989 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Language Teaching Plans, 1981-1983 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Lapham Hall Dedication Lectures, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Law Studies Program, 1972-1989 (Box 22, Folder 16-23)
    - Library, 1972-1984 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Life Sciences & Allied Health Building, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Linguistics Symposium, 1982-1988 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Literature in Transition Committee, 1970-1978 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Long-Range Academic Planning Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 22, Folder 27-29)
    - LS Scholastic Affairs Newsletter, 1970-1982 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Majors in L & S, 1973-1978 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Management Science PhD, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Mark Twain Symposium, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Master of Arts in Foreign Languages and Literature
      - 1973-1986 (Box 23, Folder 1-14)
      - 1988-1991 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Five-Year Planning Document: 1986-1987/1990-1991, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Masters of Public Administration Program, 1978-1986 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Masters Program Audits, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 17-18)
    - Mathematics Proficiency Committee, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Medical Record Administration, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Medical School, 1969-1971 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Medical Technology Program
      - 1958-1966 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - 1972-1975 (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - Proposal, 1972-1974 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Memos
      - 1956-1965 (Box 23, Folder 25-32)
      - 1966-1979 (Box 24, Folder 1-24)
      - 1980-1985 (Box 25, Folder 1-7)
    - Mentor Project, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Merger, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Meteorology, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Microcomputers, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Middle Eastern and North African Studies, 1971-1986 (Box 25, Folder 12-16)
    - Midwest Institute on Drug Abuse, 1974-1979 (Box 25, Folder 17-19)
    - Midwest Sociological Society, 1968-1969 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Milton Tercentenary Conference, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Milwaukee (City), 1961 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Milwaukee Humanities Program, 1975-1984 (Box 25, Folder 23-30)
    - Milwaukee Institute of Technology, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Milwaukee Journal Series on UWM, 1978 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Milwaukee Public Schools, 1963-1965 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Mining & Mineral Institute, 1975-1978 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Minority/Disadvantaged Student Programs, 1976? (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Minority Students
      - 1970-1974 (Box 25, Folder 34)
      - 1974-1984 (Box 26, Folder 1-4)
    - Mission Statements and Miscellaneous Reports, 1972-1979 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976-1989, undated (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Modern Studies Program, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Monterrey Institute of Technology, 1977-1982 (Box 26, Folder 6-7)
    - Museology, 1964-1971 (Box 26, Folder 8-9)
    - Museum Studies Program, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - National Science Foundation, 1961-1965 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Native American Studies Program
      - 1969-1984 (Box 26, Folder 12-20)
      - 1973-1977, undated (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Resource Directory of American Indian Professionals, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Natural Sciences, 1974-1978 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Natural Sciences and Engineering Subcommittee, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Nature Conservancy, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Nelson, Gaylord, 1966-1967 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Newberry Library, 1978-1989 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Nominating Committee, 1968-1980 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Non-Department Instructional Programs, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - North Central Association Accreditation, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Occupational Therapy Program, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Operation Wednesday, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Overload Pay, 1966-1968 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Parkinson, George A., 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Part-Time Study Opportunities, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Peace Corps, 1962-1967 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Peace Studies Program, 1990-1999 (Box 83, Folder 23)
    - Personnel Policies and Procedures
      - Memoranda Dealing with Personnel Matters, 1971-1983 (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - Tenure, 1970-1973, 1980-1981 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - PhD Output Report, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - PhD Phase-Out Simulation, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1967-1981 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Philosophy-Allied Health Cooperative Teaching Venture, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Physical Education, 1958-1963 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Pilot Project for Students from Inner City, 1969-1971 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Planning and Development, 1963-1964 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Planning Commission, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Policies and Procedures, 1967-1972 (Box 27, Folder 4-7)
    - Polish Studies, 1974-1986 (Box 27, Folder 8-9)
    - Professorship in Arabic and Islamic Civilization, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Proficiency Test, Discussion, 1977 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Program and Budget Advisory Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Program Assessment Plans, 2003-2014
    - Proposal for a Bachelor of Arts in Afro-American Studies, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Proposal for Reorganization of the M.A. Programs in Comparative Literature, French, German, and Spanish into M.A. in Foreign Language and Literature, undated (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Proposal for Reorganization of PhD in Botany into PhD in Biological Sciences, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Proposal for the Doctor of Philosophy in Geosciences, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Proposal for the Doctor of Philosophy in Urban Social Institutions, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Publications Conference, 1948-1954 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Purposes and Objectives of the College of L & S, 1984-1987 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Ranking of PhD Departments, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Reading Between the Lines, 1987-1988 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Registration Procedures, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Regulations, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Religious Studies, 1975-1977 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Religious Studies Committee, BA/MA Proposals, 1974-1983 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Religious Studies, Correspondence, 1966-1973 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Remedial Education Task Force, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Remodeling Projects, 1978-1982 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Research Incentive Program, 1983-1985 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Resource Planning Documents, 1997-1999 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Retirement Ceremony, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Review of the Master of Arts in Comparative Literature, 1973? (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Rhetorics of Technology, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Richard Peltz Memorial Fund, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Roeming, Robert, 1974-1986 (Box 27, Folder 22-23)
    - ROTC
      - 1957-1966 (Box 27, Folder 24)
      - 1978-1985 (Box 27, Folder 25)
      - Rules Governing the Faculty, 1973-2005
      - Summer Camp, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 26)
      - Summer Camp, Photographs, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Russian and East European Studies Committee, 1972-1986 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - S.A.K. Inc., 1979-1981 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Saturday Classes, 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Scandinavian Studies Group, 1976-1983 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Scholarly Activities Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - School of Allied Health Professions, 1972-1979 (Box 27, Folder 32-33)
    - School of Business Administration, 1966-1982 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - School of Education
      - 1956-1966 (Box 27, Folder 35)
      - 1970-1982 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - School of Fine Arts, 1962-1966 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - School of Library and Information Science
      - 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 38)
      - 1973-1978 (Box 28, Folder 1-6)
      - Masters Degree Proposal Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Search and Screen Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - School of Nursing, 1957-1982 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Science and Engineering Exposition, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Science Development Program
      - 1965 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Photographs, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Second Century Campaign, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Secretary of the Faculty, 1959-1964 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Secretary of the University, 1969-1985 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Shakespeare Valiorum, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Shaw Distinguished Professorship, 1983-1985 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Simultaneous Interpretation Facility, 1969-1986 (Box 28, Folder 17-21)
    - Social Science Research Facility
      - 1967-1986 (Box 28, Folder 22-28)
      - Planning Document, 1983-1984 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Social Sciences, 1954, 1972-1989 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Soils Laboratory, 1979-1986 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Soviet Seminar, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Spanish Speaking Outreach Institute
      - 1971-1978 (Box 28, Folder 32-34)
      - 1979-1985 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Advisory Committee, 1972-1986 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Summer Sessions, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Speech Communication for Business and Industry Advisory Board, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Speeches, 1957-1962 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Staff Meetings, 1969-1976 (Box 29, Folder 6-8)
    - Statistical Analysis, 1959-1968, 1988-2001 (Box 29, Folder 9-11)
    - Statistical Reports, 1965-1971 (Box 29, Folder 12-15)
    - Student Academic Services and Special Programs
      - 1979-1985 (Box 29, Folder 16-17)
      - Planning Document, 1986-1991 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Student Advisory Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Student Affairs
      - 1958-1965 (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Student Evaluation of Courses, 1963-1966 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Student Needs Project, 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Summer Session
      - Compensation, 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 23)
      - 1957-1966 (Box 29, Folder 24-25)
      - 1978-1985 (Box 29, Folder 26-27)
    - Surface Studies, 1966-1968 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Surface Studies Laboratory, 1972-1984 (Box 29, Folder 29-30)
    - Target M.D. Program
      - 1973-1981 (Box 29, Folder 31-35)
      - 1982-1986 (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
    - Task Force in Art History, Philosophy, and Religious Studies, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Task Force in Computer Science Programs, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Task Force in Divisional Structure and Function, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Task Force in Languages, Linguistics & Literature, 1968-1972 (Box 30, Folder 4-5)
    - Task Force on Enrollment Trends, 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 8-10)
    - Task Force on Urban Environmental Studies, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Task Force to Study the Feasibility of Forming a Department of Language, Literature and Linguistics, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Teacher Certificate by Exam, 1958-1961 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Teaching Evaluations, 1970-1982 (Box 30, Folder 14-16)
    - Technical Writing Workshop, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Ten-Year Building Needs, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Ten-Year Plans